>>Diamond.rip HD 720p<<
>> Diamond.rip 高清 720p <<
[creaking]
[吱吱]
[cathy]:
People use the color yellow
[凱茜]：
人使用顏色黃色
To symbolize hope.
,象徵著  的希望。
Yellow...
黃......
Like the sun
we rarely saw.
像太陽
我們很少看到的。
When I was very young,
在很小時候,
I thought life would be
我以為生活會
Like one long and perfect
summer day.
喜歡一個長和完美
夏季的一天。
After all,
it started out that way.
畢竟,
起步,它那種方式。
We were
four beautiful children
我們被
四大美女兒童
With blond hair
and porcelain skin.
金髮的
和瓷皮膚。
We looked like
those fancy dresden dolls
我們看起來像
那些花哨的德累斯頓娃娃
That grace shelves
and mantels.
恩典貨架
和壁爐。
Only we weren't just admired.
僅自己們不只是欽佩.
We were really loved.
我們真的很愛.
But that was before.
,但那是以前。
"life is full of surprises,"
my mother used to say.
"生活是充滿了驚喜,"
我的媽媽總是說。
And greed and fear and shame,
as I soon learned.
和貪婪和恐懼和羞恥,
,我很快就學會了.
And hopelessness.
和絕望.
[creaking]
[吱吱]
[d]
[] d
We never colored
even one of our paper flowers
我們永遠不會色的
甚至之一我們紙花
Yellow.
黃色.
[d]
[] d
Give them back,
christopher.
給他們回來了,
克里斯多夫。
Not until you quit
pounding on my wall, you freak.
直到你戒掉
敲打我的牆上,你嚇到。
[twins giggling]
[雙胞胎咯咯地笑]
Hey. What do you kids
think you're doing?
嘿。你做什麼的孩子
認為你在做嗎？
I don't even get a hug?
我甚至要一個擁抱嗎？
-[laughter]
-dad!
-[笑聲]
-爸爸 ！
Daddy!
爸爸 ！
Oh! I missed you all
so much!
哦 ！我錯過了你所有
這麼多啊 ！
[twins]: What did you
bring us?
[雙胞胎]:你是怎麼
帶給我們嗎？
[lid thumps]
[蓋重擊]
For you, son.
為你,兒子。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Did you
forget about me?
沒有你
忘了我嗎？
[chuckling]
[笑]
Mm!
Mm ！
I could never
forget about you.
我不可能
忘記你。
It's so beautiful.
它是如此美麗。
[d]
[] d
[kids laughing and giggling]
[孩子們笑笑]
Oh! I got you!
哦 ！我想你 ！
[laughter]
[笑聲]
Oh!
哦 ！
[all chuckling]
[所有格格地笑著]
I wish you never
had to go away
我希望你永遠不會
不得不離開
For work again.
再一次的工作。
Promise me
you won't.
答應我
你不會。
I hate to break up the party,
我不願分手聚會,
But dinner's almost ready,
and I made your favorite--
但晚餐的幾乎準備好了,
而你的最愛 — —
Homemade apple pie.
自製的蘋果派。
Corrine,
you shouldn't have.
組織,
你不應該有。
She didn't.
她沒有。
You forgot to
take off the bakery label.
你忘了
脫掉的麵包店標籤。
Ugh. Cathy! Could never
get anything past you, huh?
呃。凱茜 ！從來就不可能
有什麼過去的你,是吧嗎？
Yeah, mom.
是的媽媽。
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事？
I mean, you're wearing
a new dress and perfume.
我的意思是,你穿的
一件新衣服和香水。
Well, the wife
of a vice-president
嗯,妻子
一名副主席
Can't wear
just any old thing.
不能穿
只是任何舊的東西。
I was gonna wait
until it was 100% official,
我會等待
直到它是 100%官方,
But I got promoted,
但我得到了晉升,
And I'm now the head of sales
of the entire east coast.
我現在銷售主管
整個東海岸。
That's great!
真棒！
[dad]: Thank you.
[爸爸]:謝謝你。
[corrine]: He got promoted!
[組織]:他升職了 ！
He's so smart, that's why.
他是如此聰明,這就是為什麼。
[sniffling]
[鼻塞]
[knocking]
[敲門]
Nobody's here.
沒有人在這裡的。
Cathy...
凱茜......
Hey.
嘿。
[sighs softly]
【 輕聲歎息]
This is a big
opportunity for me.
這是一個很大
給我的機會。
For all of us.
對於我們所有人。
I know what's
gonna happen.
我知道什麼的
將要發生。
You'll be away
all the time.
你會走了
一直以來。
Mom will be busy
with the twins.
媽媽會很忙
與這對雙胞胎。
Christopher will act like
he's the man of the house.
克里斯多夫就會像
他是房子的人。
[sighing]
I'll be totally forgotten.
[歎息]
我會完全忘了。
Can I tell you a secret?
我可以告訴你一個秘密嗎？
I bought this...
我買了這個......
On my last trip,
我最後一次出差
And it's more money
than I should've spent,
它是更多的錢
比我應該已經花了,
But the moment
I saw it,
但此刻
我看到了,
I knew you
had to have it.
我知道你
必須有它。
[chuckles softly]
[輕聲笑]
So, when I'm traveling,
所以,當我去旅行,
I need you
to be strong.
我需要你
要堅強。
Can you do that for me?
你能為我做的嗎？
Mommy!
Cathy's hurting me!
媽媽 ！
凱茜的弄疼我了 ！
It wouldn't hurt so much
它不會傷害這麼多
If you'd sit still
for five seconds.
如果你仍然會坐
五秒鐘。
Girls, please.
女孩,請。
Your dad's gonna be home
in less than two hours,
你爸爸要回家
在不到兩個小時,
I need to ice the cake,
chill the champagne--
我需要冰蛋糕,
冰鎮香檳 — —
Where are your brothers?
你的兄弟在哪裡？
Why do I have to
wear a tie?
為什麼我要
打領帶嗎？
'cause we're
the "dresden dolls."
因為我們都是
"德累斯頓玩偶"。
I don't wanna
be a doll.
我不想去
是一個娃娃。
It's just a saying,
darling.
它是只是說說,
親愛。
Because the neighbors
think we look so perfect.
因為鄰居們
想我們看起來如此完美。
[chuckles]:
We are perfect.
[笑]：
我們是完美的。
[music plays on the stereo,
people chatter]
[音樂演奏了音響,
顫振的人]
[d]
[] d
Why isn't
he here yet?
為什麼不是
他還沒來嗎？
He's probably just
stuck in traffic.
他可能只是
路上堵車了。
When are we gonna
eat the cake?
我們到什麼時候
吃蛋糕嗎？
I want it now!
我現在想要它 ！
Can I take off
my tie, please?
我可以脫掉嗎
我的領帶,請嗎？
Just be patient,
darlings, okay?
只是要有耐心,
親愛的好嗎？
I'm going to go
freshen the ice.
我要去去
清新冰。
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等待、 等待、 等待、 等待、 等待。
-[car door shuts]
I hear someone in the driveway.
-[汽車門一關]
我聽到有人在車道上。
[excited murmuring
and bustling]
[興奮的喃喃低語
和繁華]
[door creaks open]
[門吱呀地打開]
[footsteps approaching]
[走近的腳步聲]
Mrs. Dollanganger?
Dollanganger 夫人嗎？
I'm sorry, but, um...
我很抱歉,但是,呃......
There's been
an accident.
已有
一次事故。
[d]
[] d
Mama?
媽媽嗎？
[d]
[] d
Mom?
媽媽嗎？
Alright, guys,
five more minutes.
好吧,夥計們,
五分鐘。
Is daddy
coming home tonight?
是爸爸
回家今晚嗎？
No.
號
Remember? We told you.
還記得嗎？我們告訴你。
He died.
他死了。
Sometimes,
when I really miss him,
有時,
當我真的很想念他,
I just pretend
he's on a business trip
我只是假裝
他是在出差
And that he'll
be back any day.
和他,他會
會回來的任何一天。
You guys wash up for dinner.
你們去洗洗吃晚飯。
[footsteps]
[腳步]
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
Mom, um, the twins want you
to read them a story.
媽媽,嗯,這對雙胞胎想你
他們讀一個故事。
Is that the mail?
這是郵件嗎？
Madame pomfrey says
龐弗雷夫人說
I can't stay
in ballet class,
我不能留
在芭蕾課,
Unless we pay
for last month.
除非我們支付
最後一個月。
Are we gonna be
okay without dad?
我們將要嗎
沒有爸爸好嗎？
I'm doing
the best I can.
我在做
盡我所能。
It's not easy
for a woman to get a job
它並不容易
一個女子去找一份工作
And to support four kids
on her own.
並支援四個孩子
她自己。
Look at me,
I'm an ornament.
看看我,
我是一種裝飾品。
The only thing
I was ever good at
唯一的事
曾經很會
Was being pretty.
我是漂亮。
You know...
你知道的。。。
You're lucky.
你很幸運。
You had a dad that
thought you were special.
你有一個爸爸,
還以為你是特別。
Because I'm just like you.
因為我只是喜歡你。
Well, in looks, maybe,
嗯,看起來,或許,
But you're more aggressive
and determined.
但你就是更具侵略性
和堅定。
You're just like his mother,
你就像他的母親,
And he loved
his mother.
他愛
他的母親。
Doesn't everyone
love their mother?
每個人都不會
愛自己的媽媽嗎？
Some mothers
are impossible to love.
一些母親
是不可能去愛。
They don't act like
mothers at all.
他們不像
在所有的母親。
Have christopher read
the twins a story,
有克里斯多夫 · 閱讀
這對雙胞胎的故事一
And put this in
the mailbox for tomorrow.
並把這放在
明天的郵箱。
Another one?
But you already sent--
另一個嗎？
但你已經發送了 — —
It's late.
You should finish your homework.
很晚了。
你應該完成你的家庭作業。
Cathy, christopher!
Come inside, now.
凱茜,克里斯多夫 · ！
現在裡面,來。
You know
all those letters I sent?
你知道的
所有這些信都是我送的嗎？
Well, I finally got a response.
好了,我終於得到了回應。
It's all working out
as I'd hoped.
它是所有工作
我所希望。
We can go live with
your grandmother,
我們可以去住在一起
你的祖母,
In virginia.
在弗吉尼亞州。
What grandmother?
什麼奶奶？
You and dad said
你和爸爸說
That we never
had any family.
我們永遠不會
有任何家庭。
Well...
嗯......
It's complicated.
這很複雜。
My parents and I,
we didn't see eye-to-eye,
我父母和我,
我們沒有看到眼對眼
So we thought it was best
to keep our distance,
所以我們認為它是最好的
要保持我們的距離,
But with your father gone,
但與你的父親走了,
This is our best hope
for now.
這是我們最好的希望
目前為止。
What about school?
學校怎麼樣？
And all
of our friends?
和所有
我們的朋友嗎？
My ballet classes?
我的芭蕾舞課嗎？
You two are old enough
to understand,
你兩個就夠老
要理解,
To help your mother
out of a desperate situation.
來?明你的母親
從絕望的境地。
But we still
have the house,
但是我們仍然
有的房子,
And I can get a part-time job,
我可以得到一份兼職的工作,
Cathy can help out more
with the twins.
凱茜可以?明更多
與這對雙胞胎。
[corrine sighs]
[組織歎息]
People have
a way of believing
人有
相信一種方式
That nothing bad
can ever happen.
這沒有什麼不好
可能發生。
And your father
was doing so well
和你的父親
做的真好
At his job, so...
在他的工作,所以......
We charged
against our future.
我們被控
對我們的未來。
What do you mean?
你是什麼意思？
Nothing here
is really ours.
這兒什麼也沒有
真的是我們。
Not the furniture,
the cars, your toys...
沒有家具,
汽車,你的玩具......
N-not even
this necklace.
即使是 N-不
這條項鍊。
It's been four months,
已有四個月,
And I've been
holding them at bay,
曾經歷過
他們舉行灣,
But the bank is gonna
come and take it all away.
但是,銀行會去
來,把一切都帶走。
Look, I know it sounds scary,
你看,我知道這聽起來嚇人,
But I've saved the best news
for last.
但我已經保存的最好的消息
留到最後。
My family is rich.
我的家庭是豐富的。
Not middle-class rich,
but unbelievably wealthy,
不是中產階級富有,
但令人難以置信的富裕,
And they have one of the finest
homes in all of virginia,
他們有一支優秀
在弗吉尼亞州的所有的家園
With servants,
僕,
And acres of land,
and their very own lake.
和英畝的土地,
和他們自己的湖。
Wait till we tell
everyone at school.
等到我們告訴
學校裡的每個人。
We leave tonight.
我們今晚離開。
Tonight?
今晚嗎？
It's our only choice.
它是我們唯一的選擇。
I know it's hard,
我知道這很難,
But I promise you,
但我答應你,
Whatever you leave behind,
不管你留在身後,
I'll buy you a thousand more
in virginia.
我會給你買一個一千年
在弗吉尼亞州。
You won't miss a thing.
你不會錯過一件事。
Don't worry, mom.
別擔心,媽媽。
We're dollangangers.
我們 dollangangers。
We'll be happy wherever.
我們將快樂無論到哪裡。
I knew I could count
on you, christopher.
我知道我可以算出
對你,克里斯多夫。
And one more thing...
還有一件事......
Our name
isn't really dollanganger.
我們的名字
真的不是 dollanganger。
It's foxworth.
它的福克斯沃思。
[train rumbling over tracks]
[火車隆隆聲曲目]
[christopher]:
I bet the house is huge.
[克里斯多夫]：
我敢打賭這房子是巨大的。
I mean, you could have
your own dance studio
我的意思是,你可以有
你自己的舞蹈工作室
With costumes
and a grand piano.
與服飾
和一架鋼琴。
I wouldn't even
hear you.
我不會連
聽你的話。
You'll be out exploring
the woods and the lake.
你會出去探索
森林和湖泊。
Way better
than any boring biology class.
更好的方式
比任何無聊的生物課。
Ma'am?
夫人嗎？
We'll reach your depot
in a few minutes.
我們就會到達您的倉庫
在幾分鐘。
Thank you.
謝謝。
You're sure
you wouldn't rather
你確定
你不會寧願
Get off
in charlottesville?
下車
在夏洛特維爾嗎？
It's 3:00 a.M.,
這是 3:0,上午,
In the middle
of nowhere.
在中間
地方。
Oh, thank you.
We have someone meeting us.
哦,謝謝你。
我們有人接我們的。
Just the children's bag.
只是孩子們的書包。
Someone will
pick up mine tomorrow.
有人將
明天去接我的。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Have a good night.
有一個美好的夜晚。
Godspeed,
mrs. Patterson.
一路平安,
派特森夫人。
[engine chugging]
[引擎突突]
I thought you said
我以為你說
There was someone
meeting us.
有人
接我們。
We should be there
before the sun breaks.
我們應該有
前太陽休息。
It's a long walk.
它是長時間地散步。
How long?
多久？
I can't carry
the twins.
我搬不動
這對雙胞胎。
Well, let them walk.
好吧,讓他們走。
The country air
will do them good.
鄉村的空氣
他們會有好處。
[d]
[] d
[carrie]: Where are we going?
I wanna go back home now!
[凱莉]:我們要去哪裡？
我想現在回家去 ！
Just a little further,
and everything will be alright.
進一步,只有一點點
和一切都會好起來。
You really think so?
你真的這麼想嗎？
Yes. If that's
what mom said.
是啊。如果那的
媽媽說什麼。
[d]
[] d
This is
foxworth hall.
這是
福克斯沃思的大廳。
[d]
[] d
Okay, cory,
blow your nose, okay?
好了,寇里,
吹你的鼻子,好嗎？
Okay. Good. Good.
好吧。很好。很好。
Okay, cathy,
button this button.
好吧,凱茜,
按鈕這個按鈕。
[door creaks open]
[門吱呀地打開]
Hello, mother.
你好,媽媽。
[thumps door shut]
[捶門關]
Well...
嗯......
Look what the cat dragged in.
看看那只貓拖著。
[grandmother]: Shh.
[外婆]:噓。
[d]
[] d
Shh.
噓。
[d]
[] d
Thank you for
taking us in, mother.
謝謝你
以我們的母親。
I don't know
what we would've done.
我不知道
我們會做些什麼。
I'm not your father, corrine.
我不是你的父親,組織。
Your groveling
has always bored me.
你卑躬屈膝
已總是使我厭煩。
I see your children
have inherited your good looks.
我看到你的孩子
有繼承你的美貌。
I just hope there's
no hidden defect or affliction.
我只是希望有
沒有隱藏的缺陷或苦惱。
I didn't agree
to run a circus here.
我不同意
在這裡跑一個馬戲團。
My children are perfect,
physically and mentally.
我的孩子是完美的
身體上和精神上。
They just need some rest.
他們只被需要一些休息。
Well, the two older children
can't share a bed.
好吧,兩個大孩子
不能分享一張床。
Cathy and christopher
are children.
凱茜和克里斯多夫 ·
都是孩子。
They're innocent.
他們是無辜的。
Yes. That's what
I used to presume about you.
是啊。那是什麼
我用來假定,關於你。
Well, if you're so worried,
好吧,如果你這麼擔心,
Why don't you put them
in a separate room?
你為什麼不把他們
在單獨的房間嗎？
Heaven knows
there's enough here.
天知道
有夠在這裡。
No, this is the only safe room
不,這是唯一安全的房間
Where your father
can't hear them.
在那裡你的父親
聽不到他們。
Put the two girls in one bed
在一個床上放了兩個女孩
And the two boys
in the other one.
和這兩個男孩
在另一個。
And when your mother and I
leave here,
當我和你母親
離開這裡,
I will lock this room
from the outside,
我將把屋子鎖
從外面看,
And you will
keep the drapes closed.
你會
保持窗簾關閉。
And remember...
並記住......
God sees everything.
神看到的一切。
God sees what evil
you do behind my back.
上帝看到什麼惡
你在我的背後。
I'll wait for you
out in the hall.
等到你
在大廳裡。
[footsteps recede]
[退去的腳步聲]
[door opens and closes]
[門打開和關閉]
Grandfather doesn't
know we're here?
祖父不
知道我們在這兒嗎？
I'm sorry, I should've
told you the truth,
我很抱歉,我應該
告訴你真相,
But I didn't want you
to be frightened.
但我不想你
被嚇倒。
When I was 18, I did something
my parents didn't approve of,
18 歲時,我做了一件
我父母不同意的
So my father
wrote me out of his will.
所以我的父親
給我寫了他的意願。
Is that why she hates us?
這就是為什麼她討厭我們嗎？
She doesn't
hate you.
她不喜歡
恨你。
She's just jealous
她不過是在嫉妒
Of how much I love
you guys and your dad,
我有多愛
你們這些傢伙和你的爸爸,
How much my father
used to love me.
多少我的父親
用來愛我。
That's why we're here.
I'm gonna win him back.
這就是為什麼我們在這兒。
我要去把他贏回來。
He's gonna put us
in his will.
他會把我們放
在他的遺囑。
He's 78 years old
and he's dying,
他是 78 歲
和他快死了,
And I just need a little time
alone to reconnect with him.
我只是需要一點時間
獨自一人來和他重新連接。
How much time?
多長時間？
I don't know exactly.
我不知道確切。
Maybe a few days
or a week?
也許幾天
或一周嗎？
And when I win my father over,
當我戰勝我的父親,
I'm gonna take you all
down to meet him,
我要把你所有
下樓來見他,
And I know he'll love each
and every one of you
我知道他會愛每個
和你們每一個人
Just as much as I do.
因為我做的。
We'll be fine up here.
我們會很好在這裡。
We're foxworths.
我們 foxworths。
[relieved sigh]
[如釋重負的歎息]
And tomorrow,
和明天,
I'll bring toys and games,
我會帶的玩具和遊戲,
And I'll come visit you
as much as I can.
我會來拜訪你
就像我可以。
And just whatever you do,
只是無論你所做的
Don't make your grandmother
angry, okay?
不要讓你的祖母
生氣,好嗎？
Corrine!
組織 ！
What is that
on that child's hand?
什麼
在那孩子的手嗎？
It's a promise ring,
from my father.
這是一個承諾戒指,
從我的父親。
Give it to me.
把它給我。
Mom, she can't.
媽媽,她不能。
Dad gave it to me.
爸爸給我。
I said, give it
to me, girl!
我說的給它
對我來說,女孩 ！
Or must I speak
more...
或我必須說
更多...
Slowly?
慢慢地嗎？
[d]
[] d
And don't you ever mention
your father in this house again.
你不提
在這個房子裡又是你父親。
[huffs] come on, corrine,
that's enough.
[huffs] 來吧,組織,
這就足夠。
[whispers]: I'm sorry.
[私語]:我很抱歉。
I promise, all our dreams
are gonna come true.
我答應你,我們所有的夢想
要成真。
Just trust me.
只是相信我。
[smooch]
[接吻]
[d]
[] d
[cory]: Where's the sun?
[科]:太陽在哪裡嗎？
Is it still night?
它的寂靜的夜晚？
Cory! Don't.
寇里 ！不要。
Your food.
你的食物。
Uh! Uh-uh-uh.
Get your hands off that.
呃 ！嗚-嗚-嗯。
讓開,你的手。
That food has to last you
the entire day.
這種食物了,最後你
整個一天。
I can't be running
up and down the stairs.
我不能運行
上下樓梯。
The servants
might get suspicious.
僕人
可能會得到可疑。
There'll be eggs for breakfast,
sandwiches for lunch,
會有雞蛋的早餐,
三明治吃午餐,
And chicken for dinner,
和雞肉晚餐,
And I want you
to eat all of it.
我想你
要吃它的所有。
Don't waste one bite of it,
you understand?
不要浪費它,咬一口
你明白？
And if you're very good,
如果你是很好,
I may bring you
some fruit.
我願為你帶來
一些水果。
Thank you.
謝謝。
I've written out
a list of other rules.
我已經寫了
其他規則的清單。
First of all, you'll keep
this room neat and tidy,
首先,你會跟
這房間的乾淨、 整潔,
As if nobody lived here.
好像沒人住在這裡。
Keep your hair brushed neatly,
保持你的頭髮梳整齊,
And your bodies clean
and fully clothed.
你的身體清潔
和完全穿上衣服。
And be modest
when you go to the bathroom.
和謙虛
當你去浴室。
Girls and boys are never to use
the bathroom at the same time.
女孩和男孩是永遠不會使用
在同一時間浴室。
You older children will
keep the younger ones quiet.
你大一點的孩子會
年輕的保持安靜。
No running around
or yelling or crying,
周圍沒有運行
或大吼大叫或哭泣,
They're good kids,
他們是好孩子
But they need somewhere
to play and make noise.
但是,他們需要在某個地方
要發揮,使雜訊。
Ah. Over here, there's a...
啊。在這裡,這裡有......
Stairway.
樓梯。
Leads up to the attic.
通向閣樓上。
You want us
to play in an attic?
你想要我們
在閣樓上玩嗎？
Up there,
there will be ample room.
在那裡,
將有充足的空間。
And, the last Friday
of every month,
和的最後一個星期五
每個月,
You're to clean out
all of your things
你要清理
你所有的東西
And hide up there
和躲到那兒
While the maids
are cleaning this room.
雖然女傭
正在打掃這間屋子。
No one must ever see
or hear you.
沒有人必須見過
或聽到你。
Do you understand?
你明白嗎？
Good.
很好。
Because if your grandfather ever
discovered that you're here,
因為如果你的祖父曾經
發現你在這裡,
You'd all be thrown out
without a red cent,
你將會拋出
沒有一分錢,
But not before getting punished
for even being alive.
但在此之前得到懲罰
因為即使活著。
[d]
[] d
Carrie...
嘉莉......
You can dress up
for days in here.
你可以打扮
天在這裡了。
Hey, cor',
check it out.
嘿,哥林多前書 ',
其簽出。
You finally get
your own record player.
你最後得到
你自己記錄的選手。
But it doesn't
have a plug.
但它不是
有一個插頭。
You just have to crank it.
你只需要用搖。
[music begins to crackle]
[音樂開始裂紋]
Better hope you inherit
from this half of the gene pool.
更好的希望你繼承
從這一半的基因庫。
Like you
know anything.
像你一樣
什麼都知道。
[d]
[] d
Our entire family.
我們整個家庭。
They're all grumpy!
Like our grandma.
他們都脾氣暴躁了 ！
像我們的祖母。
They're not grumpy.
他們不是脾氣暴躁。
Guys! You gotta
come check this out.
夥計們 ！你得
來看看這個吧。
[d]
[] d
Looks we weren't
the first kids up here.
看起來我們不是
第一次孩子們在這裡。
[carrie]:
It's hot and dusty.
[嘉莉]：
它是熱和塵土飛揚。
I don't like it.
我不喜歡它。
It's not so bad.
它不是那麼糟糕。
I wanna go outside
in the garden.
我想要到外面去
在花園裡。
This is a bad place.
這是一個不錯的地方。
I want mama!
我想要媽媽 ！
Okay, we're gonna
make this a game.
好吧,我們要去
使這一場比賽。
Pretend
we're outside.
假裝
我們已經在外面。
The floor can
be the garden,
地板可以
是花園,
And the ceiling
can be the sky,
和天花板
可以是天空,
And I'll even
make a swing.
甚至會
做一個秋千。
What do you think
she meant,
你覺得怎麼樣
她的意思,
Grandfather punishing us
for even being alive?
懲罰我們的祖父
因為即使活著嗎？
She's just
trying to scare us.
她只是
想嚇唬嚇唬我們。
Then how come she said
we'd be here for months?
然後她怎會說
我們會在這裡呆幾個月了嗎？
Quit worrying.
退出令人擔憂的。
Mom's gonna take care of us.
媽媽會照顧我們。
-[snap]
-[gasp]
-[快照]
-[嘆服]
Maybe this isn't
such a good idea.
也許這不是
這種好的主意。
See? It worked.
看看嗎？它的工作。
Cory, carrie,
come try this out.
寇里,嘉莉,
來試試這個。
I'm telling you,
the week's gonna fly by.
我告訴你,
本周的會飛的。
Mom's gonna win over her dad
and we'll all be rich.
媽媽的要贏取她的爸爸
我們就會很豐富。
We'll never have to
see this attic again.
我們永遠不會到
再次見到這的閣樓。
This is cold and greasy!
I don't like it.
這是冷和油膩 ！
我不喜歡它。
Cripes, carrie.
This is all we have.
土豆片,嘉莉。
這是我們的全部。
No!
不 ！
I don't
like this either.
我沒有
像這樣。
Children, enough.
孩子們,足夠。
Wasting food...
浪費食物......
Is the devil's work.
是魔鬼的工作。
If you leave so much
as one bite of your food...
如果你離開了這麼多
作為你的食物的咬一口......
God will tell me--
上帝會告訴我的 — —
[giggling]
[笑]
...And you will be punished
...你將會被處罰
And sent
to the bowels of hell!
和已發送
到地獄的腸子 ！
[laughing]
[笑]
Mommy!
媽媽 ！
Oh, mom. Sorry.
哦,媽媽。很抱歉。
We were just
goofing around.
我們都只是
整天遊手好閒。
[cathy]: He was trying
to get the twins to eat.
[凱茜]:他試圖
讓這對雙胞胎吃。
Oh, kids, what did I tell you?
哦,孩子,做我告訴你什麼？
I just, um...
我只是,呃......
Oh, mother. Um...
哦,媽媽。嗯......
Don't be mad.
It's not their fault.
別生氣。
它不是他們的錯。
They didn't
properly understand.
他們沒有
正確理解。
They will.
他們會。
[door creaking]
[吱吱作響的門]
Mom?
媽媽嗎？
You okay?
你還好吧？
I just wanted to come
say goodnight.
只是想要來
說晚安。
How was your first day?
It wasn't so bad, was it?
你第一天感覺如何？
它不那麼糟糕,是嗎？
Mommy, we don't
like it here.
媽媽,我們不要
喜歡這裡。
It's not nice.
它不是很好。
Carrie, stop.
嘉莉,停止。
No. Cathy and christopher
are mean.
號凱茜和克里斯多夫 ·
意思。
We wanna go home.
我們想要回家。
[cory]:
With you, mama.
[科]：
與你,媽媽。
We want you.
我們想要你。
I'm sorry, darlings,
我很抱歉,親愛的
It's just, for now,
只是,現在,
You have to listen to
your older brother and sister,
你必須聽聽
你的哥哥和姐姐,
Like they're parents.
像他們的父母。
No!
不 ！
Take us out of here. Now!
帶我們離開這裡。現在 ！
Corrine!
組織 ！
Stop that child from screaming
right now.
停止那孩子從尖叫
馬上。
[shrieks]
[尖叫]
Ow! Get away from me!
噢 ！離我遠點 ！
Get! Get off!
獲取！下車！
Stop yelling!
They're only five.
別吼了 ！
他們只有五歲。
Take off your blouse
and show them
脫掉你的上衣
並向他們展示
How bad behavior is
dealt with in this house.
如何不好的行為,是
在這所房子處理的。
You can do whatever
you want to me,
你可以做什麼
你想要我,
But you can't be
cruel to my children,
但你不能
殘忍地對待我的孩子,
Or we'll leave tonight,
或我們今晚,就會離開
And you'll never see them,
or me, ever again.
你永遠不會看到他們,
或我,過一遍。
[chuckles dryly]
[冷淡地笑]
Go!
去吧 ！
[grandmother resumes chuckling]
[祖母簡歷格格地笑著]
Now take off
your blouse.
現在脫掉
你的襯衫。
[roars]: Do it!
[咆哮]:做它 ！
Take a good long look, children,
好長時間看,孩子們,
At what happens
when you disobey me.
看會發生什麼
當你違抗我的命令。
18 lashes,
18 的睫毛,
For every year she used
her wicked charms
她用每一年
她邪惡的魅力
On my husband!
我的丈夫 ！
And 20 more
和 20 更多
For every year she lived in sin
with your father.
每一年她住在罪中
與你的父親。
A marriage
that was an abomination
婚姻
那是可憎惡的事
In the eyes of the lord,
在主的眼中
With four children
有四個孩子
Spawned by the devil!
產生的魔鬼 ！
Evil...
邪惡......
From the moment
you were conceived.
從那一刻起
你被設想。
Evil!
邪惡 ！
I make the rules
in this house.
我作出的規則
在這個房子裡。
I do!
我願意！
And I execute the punishment.
行刑。
[door creaks]
[門嘎吱作響]
Figured since I couldn't
get you a real garden,
想既然我不能
給你一個真正的花園,
That you could build
a garden in the attic.
你可以建立
在閣樓裡的花園。
What about
grandmother?
怎麼樣
祖母嗎？
Won't she punish us?
她也不會懲罰我們嗎？
She's claustrophobic.
她是幽閉恐懼症。
She'll never
climb the stairs.
她再也不會
爬樓梯。
[exhales sharply]
[呼出大幅]
You should take it easy. Mom.
你應該很容易。媽媽。
It's okay.
沒關係。
It's just
a willow switching.
它只是
柳開關。
My pride hurts
worse than my back.
我的驕傲疼
更糟的是比我的背。
But why?
但是,為什麼呢？
Why did grandmother say
those things about daddy?
祖母說,為什麼
關於爸爸的那些東西嗎？
About us?
關於我們？
When I was little,
當我很小的
I turned to
my father for love.
我轉向
愛的我的父親。
We did everything
together.
我們做的一切
在一起。
Sailing
and horseback-riding,
帆船
和騎馬,
Even hunting.
甚至狩獵。
That only made my mother
more jealous.
那只會讓我的母親
更愛嫉妒。
And she took every
opportunity she could
而且她對每個
她所能的機會
To torment me
and shame me,
要再折磨我了
和羞辱我,
And she succeeded.
她成功了。
Over the years,
多年來,
My father became more
and more busy with work,
我的父親成為了更多
和更忙著工作,
And I became
我成了
More withdrawn
and lonely.
更多的撤回
和寂寞。
And into all this came
my father's half-brother.
入這一切來了
我父親的同父異母的兄弟。
His mother had recently died
and my family took him in.
他的母親最近去世
和我的家人收留了他。
He was only
a few years older than me.
他只是
比我大幾歲。
He was so handsome
and so kind, and, uh...
他是很帥
和那麼的善良,和,呃......
So full of life.
如此充滿活力。
[sad chuckle]
[傷心笑]
My father treated him
like he was his own son,
我的父親對待他
他像是他自己的兒子,
And I'd never met
anyone like him.
素未謀面
任何人都喜歡他。
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
You're talking about dad?
你談論的爸爸嗎？
We tried to keep
our feelings secret,
我們試圖保持
我們的感情秘密,
Even from each other.
甚至從彼此。
I mean, we were
related by blood.
我的意思是,我們在
血緣關係。
He was my half-uncle.
他是我的半叔叔。
And when we eloped,
當我們私奔了,
My family flew into a rage
and my father disinherited me,
我的家人勃然大怒
和我的父親我,剝奪了繼承權
And my mother said
和我媽媽說
That my children would be
born with hooved feet
我的孩子們會
出生用蹄子的腳
And forked tails.
和分叉的尾巴。
She was wrong.
她錯了。
God didn't punish me,
not with you.
上帝沒有懲罰我,
不是和你。
You are perfect.
你是完美的。
You have to believe it,
no matter what anyone says.
你要相信它,
不管別人怎麼說。
I hope you can understand
我希望你能明白
That love doesn't always come
when you want it.
愛並不總是來
當你想要它。
Sometimes it just happens,
against your will.
有時它只是發生,
違背你的意願。
I don't care what you did, mom,
or do.
我不在乎你做了什麼,媽媽,
或做。
I'll always love you.
我會永遠愛你。
Why did grandmother
let you come back?
為什麼奶奶
讓你回來嗎？
Because she's been
waiting 20 years
因為她一直都
等了 20 年
To say
"I told you so."
要說
"我告訴你"。
Trust me, cathy,
相信我,凱茜,
I'm as much a captive
of this place as you are.
我盡可能多的俘虜
這個地方作為你的是。
Hey, cor'.
嘿,哥林多前書 '。
That's a great...
這是一個偉大的......
It's a snail.
它是一隻蝸牛。
I can't wait to show it
to mama when she comes.
等不及要顯示它
給媽媽當她來了。
If she comes.
如果她來了。
She's only missed
a few days.
她只是錯過了
幾天了。
A week.
一周。
I've made a calendar.
我做了一個日曆。
You gonna help out
with the garden or what?
你要來幫忙
與花園或什麼嗎？
We need water.
我們需要水。
Watch where you're going!
看看你要去哪裡 ！
Why are you
in such a hurry?
你幹嘛呢
在如此匆忙？
Sorry, I-I just had to
get some more water
抱歉,我-我剛到
得到一些更多的水
For christopher
before the paint dries.
對於克里斯多夫 ·
之前幹的油漆。
The paint?
油漆嗎？
We're building
a garden,
我們正在建設
一座花園,
In the attic,
在閣樓上,
So the twins
won't be so scared.
所以這對雙胞胎
不會那麼害怕。
Was this
your mother's idea?
這是
你媽媽的想法嗎？
Hope you didn't inherit
her artistic abilities.
希望你沒有繼承
她的藝術能力。
The only real talent
corrine ever had was...
只有真正的才華
組織了曾經的......
For the opposite sex.
對於異性。
I'm a dancer, actually.
Ballet.
我是一名舞蹈演員,實際上。
芭蕾舞團。
And christopher's
a really good artist.
和克里斯多夫
一個真正好的演出者。
He can paint anything.
他可以畫任何東西。
Has he ever
painted you?
他曾經
畫下你嗎？
Has he asked you
to pose for him
他有問你嗎
要給他擺姿勢
With your clothes off?
與你的衣服脫掉嗎？
Come on, girl!
來吧,女孩 ！
Spill out the truth!
漏出真相 ！
I want to know what kind of
wickedness you're up to!
我想要知道什麼種
你在做的邪惡 ！
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
Nothing?
沒有什麼嗎？
Why are you trembling?
為什麼你在發抖？
Because you keep accusing us
of doing all these bad things,
因為你保持指責我們
做所有這些壞的東西,
And I don't even know
what you're talking about.
我甚至不知道
你在說什麼。
[scoffs bitterly]
[苦澀地嘲笑]
You don't know
what I'm talking about.
你不知道
我在說什麼。
Ask your brother!
問問你的兄弟 ！
He'll know.
他會知道。
By the time they're born,
他們在出生的時候
The male of the species
物種的雄性
They know all about
wickedness...
他們知道一切關於
邪惡......
Evil.
邪惡。
Right. Now, make sure
that you take all of your toys.
權利。現在,請確保
你能在所有的你的玩具。
Check under the beds.
Make sure.
檢查床下。
確保。
I don't want
any trace of you here.
我不想要
你在這裡的任何痕跡。
Why don't you take this?
你為什麼不去這？
Why does this table
look polished?
為什麼這張桌子呢
看看拋光嗎？
The room can't look
like it's just been dusted!
房間裡不能看
像它只被塵封 ！
The maids are gonna be here
in less than an hour.
侍女們都會待在這裡
在不到一個小時。
Alright, never mind.
I'll take care of it.
好吧,沒關係。
我會照顧它。
Uh--
呃 — —
Here are some real flowers
for your fake garden.
這裡有一些真正的花朵
為你假的花園。
Just go.
只是去。
"see jane run.
"看到簡運行。
Run, jane, run."
運行,簡,運行"。
Now you try.
現在,您嘗試。
No!
不 ！
We've already read it
a kazillion times.
我們已經讀過它
kazillion 倍。
[cathy]: If you guys
play nicely tonight,
[凱茜]:如果你們這些傢伙
發揮好今晚,
We can go on the roof
tomorrow morning.
我們可以在屋頂上
明天早上。
[cory]:
I don't wanna go on the roof.
[科]：
我不想走在屋頂上。
Mom!
媽媽 ！
We missed you so much!
我們錯過了你這麼多 ！
I'm sorry I've kept you
waiting so long, darlings,
對不起,我一直在你
等了這麼久,親愛的
But here's some games,
但在這裡是一些遊戲,
And the paints
you asked for, cathy.
和塗料
你問的凱茜。
Where have you been?
你去了哪裡？
I wanted
to come earlier, but...
我想要
來得更早些,但......
I've had to spend every moment
with my father.
我已經度過每個時刻
與我的父親。
You have no idea
how hard it's been on me.
你有沒有想法
如何硬它一直在我身上。
Today, I finally
今天,我終於
Just had a chance
to go sailing on the lake.
只是有一次機會
要去湖上航行。
You went sailing?
你去航海嗎？
You got some great
color, mom.
你得到了一些偉大的
顏色,媽媽。
Can you stay for
the twins' bedtime?
你可以呆嗎
這對雙胞胎的就寢時間嗎？
[twins cheering]:
Yeah! Stay! Stay!
[雙胞胎歡呼]：
是啊 ！留下來 ！留下來 ！
I have a movie date
with an old friend.
我有一個電影約會
與一位老朋友。
She keeps
asking me out
她保持
在約我出去
But I would much rather
be with you guys!
但我寧願多
和你在一起的人 ！
Then why aren't you downstairs
telling your father about us?
那麼你為什麼不到樓下嗎
你父親告訴我們的事嗎？
Well, cathy, I have to time it
very carefully.
好吧,凱西,我有時間
非常仔細。
I only just got back.
我才剛回來。
It's been a month!
已經一個月了 ！
And I'm sick of
being in here.
我已經厭倦
待在這裡。
The twins need
fresh air and sunshine.
這對雙胞胎需要
新鮮空氣和陽光。
I want to go sailing!
我想要去航海 ！
Stop picking
on mom, cathy.
停止採摘
對媽媽,凱茜。
I just want to know when.
我只是想知道什麼時候。
When are you going to tell
your father about us?
你什麼時候要告訴
關於我們你父親嗎？
When do we get to leave?
我們什麼時候離開？
Like I said,
就像我說的
My father has just
finally accepted me back.
我的父親只是有
終於接受了我回來。
Then why can't he accept us?
然後他為什麼不能接受我們？
Are we so terrible,
or stupid, or ugly,
我們是那麼可怕
或癡或醜陋的東西,
That he wouldn't want to meet
his own grandchildren?
他不會想要滿足
他自己的孫子嗎？
I can't.
我不能。
I can't tell him
about you, ever.
我不能告訴他
關於你,永遠。
My father forgave me
on one condition--
我的父親原諒了我
一個條件-
That I didn't have any children
with your father.
我沒有任何的孩子
與你的父親。
You know what?
你知道什麼？
I'll cancel
my movie date,
我會取消
我的電影約會,
And I'll stay here
with you and the twins.
我留在這裡
你和這對雙胞胎。
It's okay, mom.
這是好的媽媽。
You go.
你走。
We'll be fine here.
我們在這裡會很好。
He could go
any day now.
他可以去
現在任何一天。
That's how
heart disease works.
這就是如何
心臟疾病的作品。
A blood clot
could break free
血凝塊
可以打破免費
And find its way
to his lungs or heart,
找到它的路
他的肺或心,
Snuff him out
like a candle.
他斷氣
像一支蠟燭。
With our luck,
grandfather will never die.
我們運氣好的話,
爺爺將永遠不會死。
We'll be stuck
up here forever.
我們就會被困
永遠在這裡。
What's few more weeks?
A month, even?
什麼是幾個星期？
一個月,甚至嗎？
Pretty soon,
很快,
We're gonna be
worth millions.
我們要將
價值數百萬。
Mom already acts
like she is.
媽媽已經行為
喜歡她的是。
Have you noticed
你有注意到嗎
How she's always
in a new outfit?
她總是是如何
在一個新的衣服嗎？
She's a foxworth.
她是福克斯沃思。
She has to fit in
around here.
她的要適合
在這裡。
Cory's a cheater!
寇里的一個騙子 ！
I thought you guys were
playing hide-and-seek.
你們這些傢伙以為
玩捉迷藏。
We were!
我們了 ！
But I called and called
and he won't come out.
而被稱為被稱為
和他出不來了。
Cory!
寇里 ！
Where are you?
你在哪裡？
Christopher.
克里斯多夫。
Over here.
就在這裡。
[d]
[] d
[thud]
[砰的一聲]
[d]
[] d
It's gonna be okay.
它會沒事。
We just need to get him
warmed up.
我們只需要讓他
熱身。
[d]
[] d
Cathy?
凱茜？
I miss mama so much.
我想念媽媽這麼多。
Pretend I'm your mom.
假裝我是你媽媽。
I love you so much.
我非常愛你。
That's what makes
a real mother.
那是什麼使
一個真正的母親。
[footsteps]
[腳步]
[d]
[] d
Our first christmas
without dad.
我們的第一個耶誕節
沒有爸爸。
Remember how
he used to take us sledding
還記得如何
他用來帶我們坐雪橇
Behind the flanagans'?
背後 flanagans 嗎？
He was always
running alongside us,
他一直是
我們,一起運行
Making sure
the twins were safe.
確保
這對雙胞胎都很安全。
One christmas
up here won't matter.
一年耶誕節
在這裡不會有問題。
And we can make our own
presents for the twins.
我們可以讓我們自己
這對雙胞胎的禮物。
Say it's from santa.
說它是來自聖誕老人。
We could make something
for grandmother, too.
我們可以做些什麼
為祖母,太。
She does bring us
food every day.
她不會給我們帶來
每一天的食物。
She got us that plant.
她得到了我們那種植物。
She might even let us out.
她甚至可能讓我們。
[d]
[] d
Hurry, cathy!
快點,凱茜 ！
She's gonna
be here.
她將去
在這裡。
Careful.
I don't want it to rip.
小心。
我不想它翻錄。
Christopher,
can I have the card?
克里斯多夫
我可以卡嗎？
It has to be perfect.
它必須要完美。
[d]
[] d
Grandmother?
祖母嗎？
[d]
[] d
[card rustling]
[卡沙沙]
Cathy! Cathy!
Wake up. Santa came!
凱茜 ！凱茜 ！
醒來。聖誕老人來了 ！
This gift
is not from santa.
這份禮物
不是從聖誕老人。
It's for cory and carrie
to play pretend house,
這是寇里和嘉莉
玩假裝的房子,
Just like I did.
就像我一樣。
And all the doors and windows
really work
和所有的門和窗戶
真正的工作
And the locks.
和鎖。
I knew that color
would look perfect on you.
我知道那種顏色
看起來你的完美。
You look just like your father
when I first met him.
你看起來就像你的父親
當我第一次遇見他。
You think so?
你這麼認為嗎？
[d]
[] d
I got this
sent from paris.
我得到了這個
從巴黎寄。
It's hand-embroidered.
它是手工刺繡的。
Don't you like it?
你不喜歡它嗎？
Yes.
是啊。
I just don't know
where I'd wear it.
我只是不知道
在那裡我會穿它。
Well, I know
it's not a perfect christmas,
嗯,我知道
它不是一個完美的耶誕節,
But I still have
one more trick up my sleeve.
但仍有
一個多招了我的袖子。
A window
to the outside world.
一個視窗
到外面的世界。
My father
gave it to me.
我的父親
把它給了我。
But that's not all.
但那不是全部。
Bart, mr. Winslow,
he says that my father
巴特,溫斯洛先生,
他說,我的父親
Has an even bigger
surprise for me.
有的甚至更大
給我的驚喜。
Who's mr. Winslow?
溫斯洛先生是誰？
He's my father's attorney.
他是我父親的律師。
He says it's only a matter
他說,它只是一個問題
Of drawing up
the new paperwork, but...
起草的
新的文書工作,但是......
I'm gonna
inherit everything.
我要去
繼承的一切。
[squeals and laughs]
[尖叫聲和笑聲]
I knew you could do it, mom.
我知道你能做它,媽媽。
He's throwing me
a party tonight,
他把我扔
今晚,一方
With champagne
and a live orchestra
香檳
和一個活樂隊
And anyone who's anyone--
和任何人 — —
-...In virginia.
-Can we come?
-...在弗吉尼亞州。
-我們能嗎？
Please?
請嗎？
We'll hide somewhere
and we'll be quiet,
我們躲在某個地方
我們就會安靜,
And no one will hear us
or see us, I swear.
沒有人會聽到我們
或者看看我們,我發誓。
I think it's too risky.
這是風險太大。
I mean, after putting
in all this time...
我的意思是,放後
在這段時間......
We haven't seen
other people in so long.
我們沒見過
其他人在這麼長時間。
It's the only thing
I really want.
它是唯一的事
我真的想。
Don't you care
if I'm happy?
難道你不關心嗎
如果我高興嗎？
Cathy, quit it.
凱茜,放棄它。
You think she's happy
你認為她是快樂
Knowing her kids
are locked up in an attic?
知道她的孩子們
被鎖在一間閣樓嗎？
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
It's okay, christopher.
好吧,是克里斯多夫。
You can come.
你能來。
You can both come.
你都可以來。
After the twins
are asleep.
這對雙胞胎後
都睡著了。
I feel like, for the first time
since your father died,
我感覺自己像,第一次
自從你父親死了,
Things are finally
looking up for us.
事情最後是
對我們來說看。
This is where I used to hide and
watch my parents' parties.
這是在哪裡我用來隱藏和
看看我父母的締約方。
Just remember
your promise, okay?
只記得
你的諾言,好嗎？
Be quiet as mice.
安靜的老鼠。
And after dinner,
晚餐之後,
Go straight back
to our room.
回的直走
我們的房間。
Yes.
是啊。
[band plays christmas music
as guests banter]
[樂隊演奏聖誕音樂
作為客人的玩笑]
[d]
[] d
[sighing]
[歎息]
The house hasn't been
so lively in years.
房子還沒有
如此熱鬧年。
And all this
because of you.
而這一切都
因為你。
That's what worries me.
這是我擔心的。
I hope I don't
disappoint anyone.
我希望我不
讓任何人失望。
Oh, no, miss foxworth,
you're as lovely as ever.
哦,沒有,小姐福克斯沃思,
你像以前一樣可愛。
Thank you, sarah.
謝謝你,莎拉。
[background chatter]
[背景聲]
That dress...
那件衣服......
Most women would be
too modest to wear it.
大多數婦女會
太謙虛了,穿上它。
I know you don't
approve of this party,
我知道你不要
批准這一方,
But try to have fun,
但嘗試玩得開心,
For father's sake.
為父親的緣故。
Your father's well-being
is my only concern.
你父親的福祉
是我唯一的擔心。
It's the one thing
we share.
這是一件事
我們分享。
Merry christmas.
祝聖誕快樂。
Corrine, this is
all too gorgeous.
組織,這是
都太華麗。
I wanted
something simpler,
我想要
更簡單的事情
But my father insisted.
但我的父親堅持說。
[corrine giggles]
[組織咯咯地笑]
Well, I always told him,
"spare the rod,
好吧,我總是告訴他,
"閑了棍子,
And spoil the child."
和慣壞了孩子。
Mother, please.
請媽媽,請。
Well, she certainly
doesn't look spoiled.
好吧,她肯定
看上去被寵壞了。
God, I can't
even imagine
上帝,我不能
甚至想像
Being invited
to a party like this.
被邀請
對這樣的聚會。
You won't have to.
你不會到。
Someday,
it's gonna be our party.
總有一天,
它要我們的党。
[bustling of guests below]
[熙熙攘攘的客人下面]
John, I told
sarah specifically
約翰,我告訴
莎拉專
To serve
the aged bourbon.
服務
歲的波旁威士卡。
I always keep
我總是保持
A few extra bottles
handy up here.
幾個額外瓶
在這裡派上用場。
I know how
mr. Foxworth enjoys it.
我知道如何
福克斯沃思先生喜歡它。
[quiet gasps]
[安靜的喘息聲]
Oh, never mind.
哦,沒關係。
It'll just make him
fall asleep before dinner.
它只會讓他
晚餐前睡著。
And john...
和約翰......
Get rid of sarah.
擺脫莎拉。
Tonight?
今晚嗎？
But, ma'am,
it's dead cold out,
但是,夫人,
它死了外面很冷,
And there are no more trains.
還有沒有更多的火車。
Well, then
that will show the servants
好吧那麼
這將表明僕人
What happens
when they don't do as I say.
會發生什麼
當他們不做像我說的。
[d]
[] d
[abruptly stops playing]
[突然停止播放]
[party chatter hushes]
[方顫振林子]
Father!
父親 ！
Merry christmas.
祝聖誕快樂。
[giggles]
[笑聲]
[gasps]
[驚歎]
It's so beautiful.
它是如此美麗。
I don't deserve that.
我不值得這樣。
It belonged to my mother.
它屬於我的母親。
Passed on
from her own mother.
通過對
從她自己的母親。
And this...
和這......
Is just the beginning.
只是一個開始。
[deflating sigh]
[消遙歎了口氣]
It's so beautiful.
它是如此美麗。
Ah.
啊。
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
Maybe someday you'll have
a daughter of your own
也許有一天你會有
你自己的一個女兒
That you can
pass it on to.
你可以
傳遞給它。
[faint strains of party below]
[微弱菌株的下面一方]
[footsteps]
[腳步]
Come on, over here.
來吧,在這裡。
[d]
[] d
You're missing
all the fun, mr. Winslow.
你錯過了
所有的樂趣,溫斯洛先生。
Come on, corrine.
來吧,組織。
Just five minutes alone.
只是呆上五分鐘。
You know
I hate big parties.
你知道的
我討厭大党。
I can't, bart.
我不能,巴特。
Everyone's
waiting for me.
每個人的
等待著我。
You must have a secret.
你必須有一個秘密。
What?
什麼嗎？
You're beautiful, smart...
你很漂亮,聰明......
Pretty soon,
you'll be one of
很快,
你就會成為其中之一
The richest women
in virginia.
最有錢的女人
在弗吉尼亞州。
That's the least
of your charm.
這就是最少
你的魅力。
How are you
so perfect?
你好嗎
如此完美嗎？
Well, I'm far from perfect.
好吧,我很不完美的。
Just ask my mother.
只是問問我的母親。
Ah, what does
your mother know?
啊,什麼呢
你媽媽知道嗎？
[giggles awkwardly]
[尷尬地傻笑]
I have to go back and be
the dutiful daughter, remember?
我要回去和會
這個孝順的女兒,還記得嗎？
I can't wait to start
our lives together...
等不及要開始
我們一起的生活......
Just the two of us.
只是我們兩個。
[cathy whispers]:
Did you hear that?
[凱茜耳語]：
你聽到了嗎？
He said "just the two of us"?
他說："只是我們兩個"嗎？
[christopher]: Well,
she's about to inherit millions.
[克里斯多夫]:嗯,
她將繼承數以百萬計。
A lot of guys
are gonna be after her.
很多男人
要追她。
We should go back
up to the room.
我們應該回去
到房間。
You coming?
你來嗎？
No. No, not yet.
號不,沒有。
I'm gonna explore the house.
我要去探索這房子。
[d]
[] d
[corrine]:
We can't do that, not tonight.
[組織]：
我們不能這樣做,不今晚
[bart]: I just want
to see this famous "swan bed"
[巴]:我只是想
來看看這著名"天鵝床"
Everybody's talking about.
每個人都在談論。
Nobody's talking
about my bed.
沒人說過
關於我的床。
[bart chuckles]
[巴特笑]
[d]
[] d
Where's christopher?
克里斯多夫在哪裡？
Where is
christopher?
在哪裡
克里斯多夫？
I don't know.
He went to look around.
我不知道。
他去看看。
Do you know
what would happen
你知道嗎
會發生什麼
If anyone found out
about you?
如果任何人發現了
你怎麼了？
Just when everything
is coming together for me?
只是當一切
來接在一起我嗎？
Mom, we were quiet.
媽媽,我們都很平靜。
No one heard us,
I swear.
沒有人聽見我們了,
我發誓。
Just for that, you will never
come out of this room.
為此,只是你永遠不會
走出這個房間。
Not for any reason!
不為任何理由 ！
How can you say that?
你怎麼可以這樣說？
You can't keep us
locked in here forever.
你不能讓我們
鎖在這裡,永遠。
[smack]
[味道]
If you ever
do that again,
如果你曾經
再,做一次
I will whip you!
我會鞭打你 ！
And cathy, too!
凱茜,太 ！
[footsteps]
[腳步]
Morning.
早晨。
What's the matter?
這件事是什麼？
Should I tell santa
to take back all your presents?
我應該告訴聖誕老人嗎
要帶回所有你的禮物嗎？
Go play.
去玩。
I'm sorry
about last night.
對不起
關於最後一夜。
I didn't mean it,
about the whippings.
我沒有這個意思,
關於鞭打。
Any of it.
任何的它。
I just-- I was scared
that you would get caught
我只是 — — 我很害怕
你會被抓住
And we would lose everything.
我們將會失去一切。
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
I would never do anything
to hurt you.
我將永遠不會做任何事
要傷害你。
You have to
believe me.
你有到
相信我。
What about bart winslow?
什麼關於巴特溫斯洛嗎？
We saw you together.
我們看到你們在一起。
Are you with him?
你是他嗎？
Well, I-I told you,
he's my father's attorney,
好的我 — — 我告訴過你,
他是我父親的律師,
And he's helping us.
他在?明我們。
You should be glad
that we've become so close.
你應該高興
我們已經變得如此之近。
This is all a mistake.
這是一個錯誤。
What?
什麼嗎？
Coming here.
來這裡。
Look what it's done to you.
看起來它對你做了什麼。
To me.
對我來說。
Let's leave, right now.
現在讓我們離開。
Start over somewhere else,
without my father's money.
在別的地方,開始
沒有我父親的錢。
No amount of money is worth
再多是錢的值得
Having my own children
not love me.
有我自己的孩子
不愛我。
Just know that,
if we leave,
只是知道的
如果我們離開,
We can never
come back.
我們永遠不能
回來。
Of course,
I love you, mom.
答案是肯定的
我愛你,媽媽。
[d]
[] d
[television]:
...A rugged design.
[電視]:
......堅固耐用的設計.
A sturdy,
lightweight steel frame...
A 堅固、
輕型鋼框架......
...On all four wheels.
......在所有四個車輪
And hydraulic brakes.
和液壓制動器.
It has
a fully automatic transmission,
它有
全自動傳輸、
And it's equipped with
aluminum-frame...
和它配備了
鋁框......
Hey.
What are you doing up here?
嘿。
什麼是你在這裡幹呢？
Sorry. I just...
很抱歉。我只是...
I just realized
we've been here an entire year.
我剛剛意識到
我們在這裡已經整整一年了。
What is that?
什麼？
It's nothing.
這沒有什麼。
Why do you want to
look at that?
為什麼你想去
看看那個嗎？
At those women?
在這些婦女嗎？
Just drop it.
只是刪除它。
[she sighs]
[她歎了口氣]
When men and women
love each other,
當男人和女人
彼此相愛,
They have feelings
他們有的感覺
In their hearts
as well as their bodies.
在他們的心
以及他們的身體。
See, at your age,
it's natural
看你的年齡,
它是自然
That your body
would start changing.
你的身體
將開始改變。
I don't want
my body to change.
我不想要
若要更改我的身體。
Well, you don't
have any choice.
嗯,你不是
有任何選擇的餘地。
It's nature's way of
making you into a woman.
自然的方式
使你變成一個女人。
You don't want to be a child
your whole life, do you?
你不想要一個孩子
你整個的生活,你有嗎？
What about
christopher?
怎麼樣
克里斯多夫？
Well, he'll have to
start shaving,
哦,他會到
開始剃須,
And there's other things
that he'll have to learn.
還有其他的事情
他將不得不學習。
Like what?
像什麼？
Kissing?
接吻嗎？
You know, I'll explain it all
to you one day.
你知道,我會解釋這一切
給你一天。
But in the meantime,
但與此同時,
I brought you all
some new clothes.
我帶給你所有
一些新衣服。
And I brought this
specially for you.
我在此提出
專門為你。
You know, you're lucky.
你知道,你很幸運。
At your age, I had no one
to come to with these questions.
在你這個年齡,我也沒有
帶著這些問題來到。
[footsteps receding]
[漸漸退去的腳步聲]
[gasps]
[驚歎]
What're you doing?
你在做什麼？
You look so, uh...
你看起來這麼,嗯......
[footsteps]
[腳步]
Ah.
啊。
I knew I'd catch you
sooner or later.
我知道我會抓住你
或早或晚。
We weren't
doing anything.
我們不是
做任何事情。
You think
you look so pretty
你認為
你看起來很美
In your new young curves
在你新的年輕曲線
And your long,
golden hair.
和長貴,
金色的頭髮。
[snaps] how many times
have you allowed your brother
[快照] 多少次
你允許你的哥哥嗎
To use you?
要使用你嗎？
Use?
使用嗎？
What do you mean?
你是什麼意思？
I walked in
on cathy by accident.
我走在
在凱西的事故。
We haven't done
anything wrong.
我們沒有做過
什麼都錯了。
Your sister is almost naked.
你妹妹是幾乎一絲不掛。
And she allowed you
to look upon her body!
她允許你
看著她的身體 ！
Sit down, girl.
坐下來,女孩。
What're you doing?
你在做什麼？
I am going to cut off
your precious hair
我要去剪掉
你珍貴的頭髮
Down to the scalp.
到頭皮。
Maybe then you won't
feel so much pride
也許你也不會
感覺到這麼多的驕傲
When you look
in the mirror.
當你看著
在鏡子裡。
[gasps]
[驚歎]
You're not gonna cut
one strand of cathy's hair.
你不會削減
一縷凱茜的頭髮。
Oh?
哦？
Alright, then.
Have it your way.
好了,然後。
有你的方式。
Her hair...
她的頭髮......
Or the four of you
don't eat for a week.
或四個你
不要吃了一個星期。
But the twins...
They didn't do anything.
但這對雙胞胎......
他們沒有做任何事情。
I think
it'll be your brother
我認為
這將是你的兄弟
Who will cut off
your precious hair.
誰將會切斷了
你珍貴的頭髮。
Or none of you will eat at all.
或者你們誰都不會吃任何東西。
I'm still hungry.
我還餓著呢。
Me too.
我也是。
I want
a sandwich now.
我想要
現在一份三明治。
We just need to ration
what we have.
我們只需要定量配給
我們所擁有。
Until mom comes back.
直到媽媽回來。
You guys
can have my crackers.
你們這些傢伙
可以吃我的餅乾吧。
How could
she do this to us?
如何能
她對我們這麼做嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
No!
不 ！
We're innocent.
我們是無辜的。
She can't control us.
We can't let her.
她不能控制我們。
我們不能讓她。
The twins
don't look good.
這對雙胞胎
看起來不好。
I can check the mouse
traps in the attic.
我可以檢查滑鼠
在閣樓上的陷阱。
[d]
[] d
[gasps in horror]
[在恐怖片中的喘息聲]
I think it's tar.
我認為它的焦油。
It's not coming out.
它不出來了。
I tried everything
我試過一切
From the chemistry kit
mom gave me.
從化學試劑盒
媽媽給了我。
You'll have to
use the scissors.
你就得
使用剪刀。
[water splashing]
[水濺]
[snip]
[剪斷]
It wasn't your fault.
它不是你的錯。
All you did
was look at me.
你所做的一切
是看著我。
I try so hard
not to think about girls.
我如此努力
不去想的女孩。
I just wish to god
you weren't so...
我只是希望向上帝
你不是這樣......
Close.
關閉。
Then you do
think of me?
然後你做
想想我嗎？
You think I'm pretty?
你覺得我漂亮嗎？
Yeah. Uh...
是的。呃......
You're pretty, but...
你很漂亮,但是......
Brothers don't think
of their sisters that way.
兄弟不認為
他們的姐妹們這種方式。
[d]
[] d
[scoffs]
[嘲笑]
No way.
不可能。
I need a dance partner
to do this next move.
我需要一個舞伴
要做這下一步的行動。
I said
I don't dance.
我說過
我不會跳舞。
Gimme that.
給我的。
[laughing]
[笑]
[shirt rips]
[襯衫撕裂]
You jerk!
This is my favorite one.
你這個混蛋 ！
這是我最喜歡的一個。
It's not my fault
you outgrew it.
不是我的錯
你容不下它。
You're outgrowing
a lot of things.
你超越
很多事情。
When are we gonna
outgrow things?
我們到什麼時候
長大的東西嗎？
No! I don't
want to go outside!
不 ！我沒有
想要到外面去 ！
You guys need fresh air
and sunshine.
你們需要新鮮的空氣
和陽光。
It's for
your own good.
它是為
你自己好。
No!
不 ！
Let them go, chris.
讓他們走,克裡斯。
They're never gonna grow.
他們永遠不會成長。
Not in this attic.
不在這閣樓。
Cathy...
凱茜......
We're getting out of here.
我們要離開這裡。
[d]
[] d
[rope softly thuds below]
[繩索輕輕地砰砰聲下面]
[d]
[] d
Cathy, come on!
凱茜,來吧 ！
1:00:40,737-1:00:43,005->
[尖叫聲和笑聲]
[shrieks and laughs]
[d]
[] d
[cathy]:
Where do you think mom is?
[凱茜]：
你在哪裡想媽媽是？
I don't know.
我不知道。
It's been over a month.
已經超過一個月。
She's never been
gone that long.
她從來沒有
走了那麼長的時間。
Why didn't she tell us
where she was going?
她為什麼不告訴我們呢
她要去哪裡？
Wherever she is,
不管她在哪,
I'm sure
she's thinking of us.
我敢肯定
她我們的思維。
Do you still trust her?
你仍然相信她嗎？
[sighs heavily]
[重重歎了口氣]
I don't even know
what I feel anymore.
我甚至不知道
我所感到的了。
I mean, I want
to trust her,
我的意思是,我想要
要信任她,
I do, but...
我做的但是......
If something
happened to her...
如果出了什麼
對她發生了......
What would
happen to us?
什麼會
發生在我們身上嗎？
[twig snaps]
[小樹枝快照]
She's so beautiful.
她是如此美麗。
Cathy, careful.
凱茜,小心。
[cathy chuckles]
[凱茜笑]
We should get back,
我們應該回去,
Before the twins
wake up.
之前這對雙胞胎
醒來。
He's trapped!
Do something!
他是被困住 ！
做些什麼 ！
Don't let him die!
I want him to be my pet.
別讓他死 ！
我想他是我的寵物。
Cory, just
don't touch him.
寇里,只是
別碰他。
You're mean!
你是這個意思 ！
You won't let
cory have anything.
你不會讓
寇里有什麼。
I'm gonna
call him mickey.
我要去
給他打電話米奇。
Careful, be gentle.
小心點,要溫柔。
Don't worry.
I'm gonna take good care of you.
不用擔心。
我要去照顧好你。
I promise.
我保證。
-[door opens]
-sweeties!
-[門打開]
-糖果 ！
I'm sorry
I was gone so long,
對不起
了這麼長時間,
But I have wonderful news!
但我有一個好消息 ！
Is it grandfather?
它是爺爺嗎？
Is he dead?
他是死了嗎？
Oh, cathy, don't be so morbid.
哦,凱茜,不要如此的病態了。
Do you remember I told you
about my father's attorney?
你記得我告訴過你嗎
關於我父親的律師嗎？
Bart winslow.
巴特斯洛。
Well, we've grown closer
over the past year,
好吧,我們已經長大,更緊密
在過去一年,
And we got married.
我們結婚了。
What?
什麼嗎？
When did this happen?
這是什麼時候發生的？
A few months ago.
幾個月前。
That's why
I was gone so long.
這就是為什麼
是走了這麼長時間。
We just got back from
our honeymoon in europe.
我們剛從回來
我們在歐洲度蜜月。
Well, I thought about you
the whole time.
好吧,我想你
整個時間。
I even got you
these beautiful presents.
我甚至想你
這些漂亮的禮物。
This is a boat
and it's called a gondola.
這是一條船
和它被稱為吊船。
You were wrong
to go away.
你錯了
要走了。
To stay away for so long.
I don't care why.
待走了那麼久。
我不想知道為什麼。
Try to be happy
for me.
試著快樂起來
對我來說。
I loved your father,
but he's gone.
我愛你的父親,
但他走了。
I need
someone to love,
我需要
愛的人,
And someone to love me.
和一個愛我的人。
When you're older,
you'll understand.
當你老了,
你就會明白。
We are older, mom!
我們   老年人,媽媽 ！
Look at us.
看看我們。
I'm not a kid anymore!
我再也不是一個孩子 ！
And cathy, does she even
look like a little girl?
凱茜,她不會連
看起來像一個小女孩嗎？
[chuckles dismissively]
[淡淡地笑]
I know
you're gonna love bart.
我知道
你要愛巴特。
I got you
this magnifying glass.
我想你
此放大鏡。
It's an antique.
這是個古董。
You said we would be up here
for one night,
你說過我們會在這裡
一天晚上,為
Then a few days, a month--
然後過幾天,一個月 — —
It's been more than
two years, mom!
它已超過
兩年來,媽媽 ！
You think your presents
are gonna make up
你認為你的禮物
想做一
For what we've lost?
為我們失去了什麼嗎？
What we're losing?
我們失去了什麼嗎？
[shatters]
[粉碎]
You have no right
to talk to me like that.
你有沒有權利
像這樣跟我說話。
You agreed to stay here
until my father died.
你願意呆在這裡
直到我父親去世了。
I said that I would
我說我願意
Take care of you,
and I have.
好好照顧你,
還有。
You have food
and books and toys,
你有食物
書籍和玩具,
And a tv set!
和一台電視機 ！
If you can't have pity for us,
think of the twins.
如果你不能有遺憾,對我們來說,
想想這對雙胞胎。
Mom...
媽媽...
They don't even know
who you are anymore.
他們甚至不知道
你是誰了。
I'm their mother.
我是他們的母親。
I'm the only person
who truly loves them.
我是唯一的人
誰真正疼愛他們。
[she sighs sullenly]
[她歎了口氣繃著臉]
All along,
I've only done the best I could.
一直以來,
我只是做的盡我所能。
You haven't even
你甚至還沒
Told bart about us.
巴特告訴我們。
Have you?
你有嗎？
He doesn't even know we exist.
他甚至不知道我們的存在。
I never could get anything
past you, could I, cathy?
永遠不能任何東西
過去的你,可我,凱茜嗎？
[key clatters in lock]
[鑰匙在鎖哢]
[door creaks]
[門嘎吱作響]
Are these donuts?
是這些甜甜圈嗎？
They're from your mother.
他們是從你的母親。
I wouldn't eat 'em,
if I were you.
我不會吃他們吧,
要是你。
They're not good
for your health.
他們不好
對你的健康。
[door creaks and thuds]
[門嘎吱作響和砰砰聲]
We could escape,
you know.
我們可以逃避,
你知道的。
We could go down
the roof again.
我們可以去
再一次的屋頂。
With the twins.
與這對雙胞胎。
I know they were
scared before,
我知道他們是
害怕之前,
But if we just
explained it...
但是,如果我們只是
解釋它......
And we can time it out
with the train.
我們可以時間,
與火車。
Don't you think
I know that?
你不覺得嗎
我知道那件事？
Then why are we
still here?
那麼為什麼我們
你還在這裡嗎？
All the money
in the world
所有的錢
在世界
Is not worth this.
不值得這樣。
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
You still believe mom?
你仍然相信媽媽嗎？
What choice do I have?
我還有什麼選擇？
[sighs]
【 歎息 】
Besides...
此外......
Where the hell are we supposed
to go from here?
在那裡我們應該下地獄
從這裡走嗎？
[gunshot fires]
[槍火]
[shot fires]
[鏡頭的火災]
[lock rattles]
[鎖搖鈴]
[door creaks]
[門嘎吱作響]
Step away
from the window, boy.
走了一步
從視窗中,男孩。
My name's not "boy."
我的名字不是"男孩"。
It's christopher.
它的克里斯多夫。
What did you say?
你說什麼？
I said my name is christopher.
我說我的名字是克里斯多夫。
The same as my father's.
就像我父親一樣。
Take off
your shirt, boy.
脫掉
你的襯衫,男孩。
I will whip your sister
and both the twins
我會鞭打你的妹妹
和這兩個雙胞胎
If you don't
take off your shirt.
如果你不
脫掉你的襯衫。
Now!
現在 ！
Cathy, go to the attic.
凱茜,到閣樓裡去。
-Don't touch him!
-Go!
-別碰他 ！
-去吧 ！
Cathy...
凱茜......
Now.
現在。
Take off your shirt.
脫掉你的襯衫。
[d]
[] d
[whip cracking repeatedly below]
[鞭開裂一再下文]
[d]
[] d
I was so scared.
於是害怕了。
I kept thinking,
我一直在想,
If something
happened to you...
如果出了什麼
發生在你身上......
Don't worry, cath'.
別擔心,cath'。
I'm right here.
我就在這裡。
[d]
[] d
I know what we did
was wrong,
我知道我們做了什麼
錯了,
But I don't care.
但我不在乎。
Felt good,
didn't it?
感覺還好,
不是嗎？
And romantic?
和浪漫嗎？
[door opens]
[門打開]
[gasps]
[驚歎]
What is the meaning of this?
意思是什麼？
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
You were right
about us all along.
你是對的
我們一直都。
We are the devil's spawn.
我們都是魔鬼的菌種。
"when someone
wants to do wrong,
"當有人
想要做錯了,
"it's never god
who's tempting him...
"它永遠不會是上帝
誰試探他......
"for god never wants
to do wrong
"為上帝永遠不會想要
做錯事
"and never tempts
anyone else to do it.
"和永遠不會誘惑
任何人去做。
"temptation is the pull
"誘惑就是拉
Of man's own evil thoughts
and wishes."
人的邪惡思想的
和祝願。
Can you ever forgive us?
你能原諒我們嗎？
Only the lord can
forgive you, boy.
只有主可以
原諒你,孩子。
Prayer is the key
to your salvation.
禱告是關鍵
向你的救恩。
[door creaks]
[門嘎吱作響]
[grandmother locks door]
[祖母鎖門]
[chuckling]
[笑]
No.
號
This is our key.
這是我們的關鍵。
This is the master key.
這是萬能鑰匙。
It should work on all the doors,
它應該工作的所有的門,
Even the front one.
即使前一。
I wish we could
run away tonight.
我希望我們能
今晚就跑了。
Well, we need money.
好吧,我們需要錢。
Lots of it.
它有很多。
So when we escape,
所以,當我們逃避,
We can go
wherever we want.
我們可以去
無論我們想要。
We can steal...
我們就可以偷......
From the house.
從那所房子。
If grandmother catches us,
she'll whip us.
如果奶奶抓住我們,
她就會打我們。
She probably keeps track
of every single penny.
她可能跟蹤
每一分錢。
But not mom.
但不是媽媽。
Dad always said
爸爸總是說
She was careless
with money.
她是太粗心了
用的錢。
Cathy, you find anything?
凱茜,你發現什麼嗎？
You didn't tell me
there was all this stuff.
你沒告訴我
有了這所有的東西。
Last time I was here,
there wasn't this much stuff.
上次我在這裡,
沒有這麼多的東西。
How do I look?
我看起來怎麼樣？
You look ridiculous.
你看起來可笑。
Now, uh...
現在,呃......
Take that stuff off
and start looking for cash.
脫下那種東西
並開始尋找現金。
We can't take too much
or she might notice.
我們不能帶太多
或者她可能會注意到。
Cathy, what's the matter?
Are you deaf?
凱茜,這件事是什麼？
你是聾子嗎？
$30.
$ 30。
That'll barely get us
to the next county.
這幾乎不會給我們
到下一個縣。
We need a thousand.
A-at least.
我們需要一千。
A-至少。
That'll take weeks.
這會需要數周。
We need to leave now.
我們需要現在就離開。
No, not till we have enough
to get away from here.
沒有,直到我們有足夠的
要離開這裡。
Cory?
寇里嗎？
Didn't I give you
my extra donut
我沒有給你嗎
我額外的甜甜圈
If you'd sit still?
如果你仍然會坐嗎？
It's mickey.
它的米老鼠。
He doesn't like
the hammering noises.
他不喜歡
錘擊的雜訊。
What are they doing?
他們在做什麼？
They're putting up a fence.
他們正在建設一個籬笆。
[d]
[] d
Alright,
you go in without me.
好吧,
沒有我,你們走。
I need to check
outside.
我需要檢查
外面。
No. What if something
happens to you?
號如果一些東西
發生在你身上嗎？
I have to make sure
we can get out.
我必須確保
我們可以走出去。
I love you,
christopher doll.
我愛你
克里斯多夫 · 布娃娃。
I love you, too.
我也愛你。
[d]
[] d
[zapping]
[電擊]
[d]
[] d
[corrine]:
Bart, you're just careless.
[組織]：
巴特,你只是粗心。
You can't find your own wallet.
你找不到你自己的錢包。
[bart]: It's not me,
it's the maids.
[巴]:不是我,
它是女傭。
I swear I left it
in my black trousers.
我發誓我離開它
我的黑褲子。
And I think they've been
stealing from us.
我認為他們已經
從我們身上偷竊。
The other day,
I was missing $5.
那天,
我錯過 5 美元。
Before that,
it was 10.
在那之前,
這是 10。
$5, $10--
what's the difference?
$ 5,$10 — —
區別是什麼？
You left me alone
at our own dinner party?
你把我獨自留下
在我們自己的晚餐聚會嗎？
It's not
exactly a party,
它不是
確切地一方,
Having to sit across
from your mother.
不必跨坐
從你的母親。
I'm sorry. You know
I want to move out of here, too,
對不起。你知道的
我想要搬離此處,太,
As soon as possible.
儘快。
Let's take a trip.
讓我們走一趟。
Babe, I can't.
寶貝,我不能。
You know how busy
work is right now.
你知道如何忙
工作是現在。
What about
a mini-vacation?
怎麼樣
迷你假期嗎？
I know a certain swan bed
that has a vacancy.
我知道某些天鵝床
那有一個空缺。
As a matter of fact,
實際上
I had the sweetest dream
earlier there today.
我做了最甜美的夢
今天早些時候那裡。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah. A beautiful
young blonde girl
是的。一個美麗的
年輕的金髮女孩
Snuck into the room,
kissed me.
偷偷溜進了房間,
吻了我。
Right on the lips.
唇。
She reminded me
of you,
她提醒了我
你,
But younger,
more innocent.
但年輕,
更多的無辜。
[d]
[] d
Wow. That must've been a dream.
哇。那一定是一場夢。
Why don't we go stay
in a hotel?
我們為什麼不去住
在一家酒店嗎？
That way, you don't have to see
my mother's face in the morning.
這樣一來,你沒有看到
我母親的臉在早上。
[bart chuckles]
[巴特笑]
[d]
[] d
How could you be
so careless?
你怎麼能
如此粗心？
I'm sorry.
對不起。
He was asleep.
他睡著了。
I was curious.
我很好奇。
You kissed that man!
你吻了那個男人 ！
And he wasn't asleep,
he saw you!
他不是睡著了,
他見到你 ！
Mom can't know
we passed through a locked door!
媽媽不知道
我們穿過一扇鎖著的門 ！
We don't have enough money yet.
我們還沒有足夠的錢。
You think you're the only one
frustrated?
你認為你是唯一一個
沮喪嗎？
Christopher! Stop!
You're hurting me.
克里斯多夫 · ！停止 ！
你傷害我。
[breathing hard]
[呼吸困難]
It's okay.
沒關係。
You didn't mean it.
你沒有這個意思。
We'll go to florida.
我們要去佛羅里達。
Sarasota...
薩拉索塔......
Where all
the circus people live.
在那裡所有
馬戲團人民生活。
Yeah.
是的。
We can star
in a freak show.
我們可以明星
在一個馬戲團。
We can pretend
this never happened.
我們可以假裝
這永遠不會發生了。
We can make sure that
it never happens again.
我們可以確保
它永遠不會再次發生。
The thing is...
的事情是......
I want to feel
this way about you.
我想要的感覺
關於你的這種方式。
I love you.
我愛你。
I don't know if I can
ever love anyone else.
我不知道是否我可以
曾經愛過別人。
[door opens]
[門打開]
Cory doesn't feel so good.
寇里感覺不那麼好。
He's been
vomiting for hours.
他一直
嘔吐幾個小時。
I think it might be
food poisoning.
我認為它可能是
食品中毒。
He needs to go
to the hospital.
他需要去
到了醫院。
Why are you just
standing there?
你只是在幹嗎
站在那裡嗎？
Don't you care
what happens to him?
難道你不關心嗎
他會發生什麼？
Have you forgotten
that you're his mother?
你忘了
你是他的母親嗎？
You.
你。
It's always you.
它永遠是你。
[smack]
[味道]
Cathy, stop!
凱茜,停下來 ！
You think
you can do anything you want
你認為
你可以做任何你想要的
And people will believe you.
人們會相信你。
They'll learn the truth someday.
他們總有一天會瞭解真相。
When your husband learns
當你的丈夫得知
You have four children
locked away in an attic,
你有四個孩子
鎖在一間閣樓裡
See how "perfect"
he thinks you really are.
看看如何"完美"
他認為真正的你。
And your father, too.
你的父親,太。
You won't inherit
one damned penny,
你不會繼承
一個該死的一分錢,
And I'll be glad!
我會很高興 ！
The girl is right,
corrine.
那個女孩是正確的
組織。
That child should go
to the hospital.
那孩子應該去
到了醫院。
[d]
[] d
[floor creaking]
[地板吱呀]
[lock turning]
[鎖車]
I drove cory to the hospital.
我開車去醫院的寇里。
How is he?
他是怎麼？
Cory had pneumonia.
寇里得了肺炎。
The doctors did
all they could, but...
醫生做了
所有他們可以,但......
It was too late.
它太晚了。
Will there be
a funeral?
會不會有
一場葬禮嗎？
He's already been buried.
他是已經被埋葬了。
[d]
[] d
[starts crying]
[開始哭泣]
[d]
[] d
[carrie bawls]
[嘉莉 bawls]
I'm sorry.
對不起。
[bawling continues]
[啼哭持續]
[cathy]: Carrie?
[凱茜]:嘉莉嗎？
Cathy.
凱茜。
Just let her be.
只是讓她。
We need to run away.
我們需要跑。
Or else we're all
gonna die like cory.
否則,我們都
去死像寇里。
Do we have
enough money?
我們有嗎
足夠的錢嗎？
We'll go tonight.
我們今晚要去。
Take everything we can.
Money, jewelry.
採取一切我們所能。
錢,珠寶首飾。
Everything.
一切。
[d]
[] d
[voice breaking]:
She's not coming back.
[聲音打破]：
她不會回來。
Is she?
她是嗎？
She's dead to us now.
她現在是我們死了。
When do we tell her?
何時我們告訴她？
After breakfast.
早餐後。
I don't want her
getting scared.
我不想她
越來越感到恐懼。
More than she has to be.
更多比她還需要有。
So we just walk right
out the front door?
所以我們只是走右
出了前面的門嗎？
We wait till dinner,
我們等到晚餐,
When all the servants and family
當所有的僕人和家庭
Are in the kitchen
or dining room.
在廚房裡
或飯廳。
So carrie and I will
go to the fence
所以卡麗和我將
走到籬笆
And you'll go to the shed
你會去棚
So you can turn off
the electricity?
因此,您可以關閉
電嗎？
Then we catch up
by the lake
然後我們能趕上
由湖
And head to the depot
for the evening train.
和車廠的頭
為乘晚上的火車。
And by the time
grandmother comes in
時間
祖母進來
With our breakfast
tomorrow,
與我們的早餐
明天,
We'll be halfway
to florida.
我們就解決了一半
到佛羅里達州。
I was thinking,
I can sell my ring.
我在想,
我可以賣我的戒指。
It's okay.
沒關係。
It's what
dad would've wanted.
它是什麼
希望我的爸爸。
You're keeping that ring.
你至少能留住那枚戒指。
Forever.
永遠。
[starts coughing]
[開始咳嗽]
[d]
[] d
I'm telling you,
I did hear someone.
我告訴你,
我聽到有人。
Must be those mice.
They make an awful racket.
必須是那些老鼠。
他們會很糟糕的球拍。
You can hear them
all the way up in the attic.
你可以聽到他們
一直到上在閣樓裡。
Mrs. Foxworth carries
enough poison up there
福克斯沃思太太進行
有足夠的毒
To kill
a german army of 'em.
要殺
德國軍隊的撲克。
Do you think miss corrine
will sell the place?
你覺得小姐嗎
會賣的地方嗎？
I doubt she'll be
making any hasty decisions.
我懷疑她會
作出任何草率的決定。
Hasty? It's been
seven months
倉促嗎？它一直
七個月
Since mr. Foxworth died.
由於福克斯沃思先生去世了。
Well, never mind that.
好吧,沒關係的。
All you maids will be
losing your job soon enough
你的女僕會
失去你的工作不夠快
If you don't
mind the silver.
如果你不
銀的頭腦。
[footfalls receding]
[漸漸退去的腳步聲]
Carrie, you gotta
eat something.
凱莉,你得
吃點東西。
You have to be strong,
for later.
你一定要堅強,
為以後。
No. Don't feel well.
號感覺不好。
I have to
take care of mickey.
我有到
照顧米奇。
Where'd you get that?
你在哪裡得到的？
I saved it for cory,
留給寇里,
For when he came back
from the hospital.
他回來時為
從醫院。
[d]
[] d
[coughing quietly]
[靜靜地咳嗽]
[d]
[] d
Cathy, we need to
leave right now.
凱茜,我們需要向
現在離開。
[sniffling]
[鼻塞]
It's mickey.
它的米老鼠。
Carrie gave him
one of cory's donuts
嘉莉給了他
寇里的甜甜圈之一
And he just started
whimpering all of a sudden--
他只是開始
突然之間,嗚咽
No. No.
That can't be right.
號號
那不是可能。
What?
什麼嗎？
The powdered sugar
on the donuts,
糖粉
關於甜甜圈,
I think
there was poison in it.
我認為
那裡是在它的毒藥。
That's why we're sick.
這就是為什麼我們討厭。
Are you saying that
our grandmother
你說那
我們的祖母
Tried to kill us?
想要殺死我們嗎？
You have a key.
你有一把鑰匙。
[door bangs shut]
[門劉海關]
Now give it to me.
現在把它給我。
No.
號
Give it to me
this instant!
把它給我
這一刻 ！
[wracked with coughing]
[充斥咳嗽]
Seed of the devil!
種子的魔鬼 ！
Give me that!
給我那個 ！
You're never gonna
leave this room!
你永遠不會去
離開這個房間 ！
[scoffing]
you're gonna hit me?
[嘲笑]
你要打我嗎？
You're gonna whip me?
Come on!
加油！
Come on. Do it.
加油。做吧。
[snickering]
[偷笑]
Beautiful, prideful.
美麗、 驕傲。
And weak!
和弱 ！
Just like your mother.
就像你的母親。
That's not true.
那不是真實的。
You were never
meant to be born.
你從來都不
意味著出生。
You're a stain
on the foxworth name!
你是一個污點
福克斯沃思的名字 ！
On the name of
the lord himself.
名稱,
主自己。
Now, if you
give me that key,
現在,如果你
給我那把鑰匙,
I may show you
a little mercy.
我可以給你看
一點點的憐憫。
Christopher...
克里斯多夫 ·......
Come on!
加油！
Christopher...
克里斯多夫 ·......
[gasps] let go!
[驚歎] 放開我 ！
Cathy, go to the attic!
凱茜,去閣樓吧 ！
No! Give me that!
不 ！給我那個 ！
Come back here!
給我回來 ！
Carrie, please!
嘉莉,請 ！
[carrie gasping]
[喘著粗氣的嘉莉]
Cathy!
凱茜 ！
[bangs door shut]
[劉海把門關上]
Why did you do that?
你為什麼做那件事？
Don't close the door.
不要關門。
I need for the door
to be open!
我需要為門
要打開 ！
No. Not the door.
號不了門。
Don't turn off
the light.
不要關閉
光。
Open the door!
Turn on the light!
打開門 ！
把燈打開 ！
I need the door
to be open!
我需要在門
要打開 ！
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
No! No! Open the door!
不 ！不 ！打開門 ！
[weeping] no!
[哭泣] 沒有 ！
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
Like you said,
就像你說的
God sees everything.
神看到的一切。
He'll punish you
for what you did to us.
他要懲罰你
為你的所作所為給我們。
To cory.
到寇里。
It wasn't me!
它不是我 ！
It was your mother
who poisoned you, not me!
是你的母親
誰毒死你,不是我 ！
It doesn't
matter anymore.
它並不
已經不再重要。
[grandmother sobbing]
[奶奶泣不成聲]
Where are you going?
你要去哪裡？
Don't go!
你不去 ！
Don't leave me!
不要離開我 ！
Help! Help!
?明！?明！
Help!
?明！
[christopher coughing]
[克里斯多夫 · 咳嗽]
[d]
[] d
Cathy, we have to go.
凱茜,我們得去。
Be right there.
有道理。
[chalk clatters]
[粉筆屐]
[d]
[] d
[rope creaking]
[吱吱作響的繩]
[gasping]
[喘氣聲]
[thud]
[砰的一聲]
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
Come on.
加油。
I'll cut the electricity
and meet you at the lake.
我會切斷電力,
和你見面,湖。
No! No!
不 ！不 ！
We're not
going without you.
我們不是
不帶你走。
Hurry!
We have to make this train.
快點吧 ！
我們要讓這班火車。
Stop!
停止 ！
Stop, if you know
what's good for you!
停下來,如果你知道
什麼是對你有好處 ！
Please...
請......
We're corrine's children.
我們組織的兒童。
My god.
我的上帝。
Go.
去。
Before I'm sent
after you!
之前派我
你先走 ！
I'll cut the power
on the fence.
我會切斷電源
在籬笆上。
Go!
去吧 ！
[chugging]
[單行道]
[d]
[] d
We never have to see
that place again, cath.
我們再也看
那個地方再一次 cath.
It's all over.
就全部結束。
[cathy]: And for the first time
in a long time,
[凱茜]: 和  第一次
在很長時間,
We felt alive,
我們覺得自己還活著,
Free.
免費.
We had everything ahead of us.
我們擁有一切我們.
But someday,
we'd see mom again.
但總有一天,
我們會再次見到媽媽.
And we'd look her
straight in the eye,
和我們將看看她
直在眼中,
The children she once loved,
她曾經深愛過的孩子,
And all our shame
and hopelessness
和我們的恥辱
和  絕望
Would become hers.
會成為她.
>>Diamond.rip HD 720p<<
>> Diamond.rip 高清 720p <<
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com